To summarize this video, The type environment gives types to the free
综上所述，文字环境将类型提供给免费的
identifiers in the current scope. And this is very important, because it doesn't even
当前作用域中的标识符。这一点非常重要，因为它甚至不会
really makes sense to talk about type checking an expression, unless we have
谈论表达式的类型检查真的很有意义，除非我们有
some information for the types of the free identifiers. And the type environment is
有关空闲标识符的类型的一些信息。类型环境为
just a way of formalizing that, of giving a name to some set of assumptions about
只是将其正式化的一种方式，给一些假设取名
what the types of those free identifiers are. Notice that the type environment is
这些空闲标识符的类型是什么。请注意，类型环境为
passed down the abstract syntax tree from the root towards the leaves. That is, as
从根到叶向下传递抽象语法树。也就是说，作为
we pass through definitions, the type environment is extended with new
我们传递定义，类型环境用新的
definitions For example, [inaudible] expressions. And so the type environment
定义例如，[听不见]的表达。因此，类型环境
will grow as you pass from the root of the abstract syntax tree down towards the
将随着您从抽象语法树的根向下传递到
leaves of the abstract syntax tree. And then the types are computed up the
抽象语法树的叶子。然后将类型向上计算
abstract syntax tree from the leaves towards the roots. So we begin at the
从叶到根的抽象语法树。所以我们从
leaves, get all the types of the leaf expressions, most of which are very easy.
叶子，得到所有种类的叶子表情，大部分都很简单。
Things like integers and string constants have the obvious types. And we just look
像整数和字符串常量这样的东西有明显的类型。我们只是看看
up the types of variables, in the type environment. And then we compute the types
在类型环境中增加变量的类型。然后我们计算这些类型
for the more complicated expressions in a bottom up fashion.
用于自下而上方式的更复杂的表达式。